<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Daniel Bruzual</title>
    <link>http://bruzual.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Daniel Bruzual</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 18:14:28 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://bruzual.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Playbook</title>
      <link>http://bruzual.me/playbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 18:14:28 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bruzual.me/playbook/</guid>
      <description>The following is a list of values that are important in my life. They are the principles that dictate how I like to live.
Compiling them into a list means that they are not only feelings or abstract ideas in my mind, but concrete ideas that I can develop further. By writing them down, I expect to remember them in everyday life.
These values have come from own experiences, and also from people I admire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salsa Dancing 💃</title>
      <link>http://bruzual.me/salsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2019 18:14:28 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bruzual.me/salsa/</guid>
      <description>Starting January 2019 I joined a Salsa class for the first time in my life. Before, I would become very anxious in situations where someone might ask me to dance. Especially coming from a caribbean country and being expected to know. Finally I decided to overcome my fears and learn. Dancing has become an incredible source of joy!
Here are some of the steps that we learnt during the courses with Janis and Zoe at Tanzhaus NRW:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I am doing now</title>
      <link>http://bruzual.me/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2019 18:14:20 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bruzual.me/now/</guid>
      <description>At the moment I am based in Helsinki but traveling quite often to Düsseldorf for work. I am working for Eficode as a senior devops consultant.
I am learning to dance salsa at Tanzhaus NRW with Janis and Zoé.
I am planning my holiday trip to Brazil in September 2019.
I am training for the Dolomyths Skyrace 23km that takes place in the Dolomites mountain range in Italy. I finally sign up, 5 years after I discovered the race online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Daniel</title>
      <link>http://bruzual.me/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2019 18:14:13 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bruzual.me/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi. I am a Software Engineer interested in automation and with a drive to create useful software. I am currently working at Eficode as a Devops Consultant. I live in Helsinki 🇫🇮 but travel quite often to Düsseldorf :de: for work.
I have studied Computer Engineeering at Universidad Simón Bolívar, and I hold a MSc. in Service Design and Engineering from the University of Trento and Aalto Universityi (Thesis).
I was born and raised in Venezuela.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>