<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Daniel Bruzual</title>
    <link>http://bruzual.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Daniel Bruzual</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2019 18:14:28 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://bruzual.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Salsa Dancing 💃</title>
      <link>http://bruzual.me/salsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2019 18:14:28 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bruzual.me/salsa/</guid>
      <description>Starting January 2019 I joined a Salsa class for the first time in my life. Coming from a caribbean country it is one of those things that I am expected to know. However, I never got around to learning. Situations where someone asked me to dance where always a source of anxiety for me.
Finally this year I decided to overcome my fears and learn. Dancing has become an incredible source of joy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now</title>
      <link>http://bruzual.me/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2019 18:14:20 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bruzual.me/now/</guid>
      <description>At the moment I am based in Helsinki but traveling quite often to Düsseldorf for work. I am working for Eficode as a senior devops consultant.
I am learning to dance salsa at Tanzhaus NRW with Janis and Zoé.
I am planning my holiday trip to Brazil in September 2019.
I am training for the Dolomyths Skyrace 23km that takes place in the Dolomites mountain range in Italy. I finally sign up, 5 years after I discovered the race online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Daniel</title>
      <link>http://bruzual.me/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2019 18:14:13 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bruzual.me/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi. I am a Software Engineer interested in automation and with a drive to create useful software. I am currently working at Eficode as a Devops Consultant. I live in Helsinki 🇫🇮 but travel quite often to Düsseldorf for work :de:.
I have studied Computer Engineeering at Universidad Simón Bolívar, and I hold a MSc. in Service Design and Engineering from the University of Trento and Aalto Universityi (Thesis).
I was born and raised in Venezuela.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>